Enough said!
Sharknado is a action, comedy, horror film directed by Anthony C. Ferrante.
A freak hurricane hits Los Angeles, causing man-eating sharks to be scooped up
in tornadoes and flooding the city with shark-infested seawater.
Surfer and bar-owner Fin sets out with his friends Baz and Nova to rescue
his estranged wife April and teenage daughter Claudia.
Finley "Fin" Shepard, played by Ian Ziering.
April Wexler, played by Tara Reid.
George, played by John Heard.
Nova Clarke, played by Cassie Scerbo.
Baz Hogan, played by Jaason Simmons.
Bobby, played by Alex Arleo.
Sharknado is a 2013 American made-for-television science
fiction comedy disaster film directed by Anthony C.
It tells about a waterspout that lifts sharks out of the
ocean and deposits them in Los Angeles.
It is the first installment in the Sharknado film series.
The movie first aired on the Syfy channel on July 11, 2013, and
stars Tara Reid, Ian Ziering, and John Heard.
It was also given a one-night-only special midnight theatrical screening via Regal
Cinemas and Fathom Events, where it earned $200,000 from 200 screenings.
The over-the-top premise and theatrics of the film
quickly earned it a cult following.
The film spawned a franchise of the same name; five sequels have been produced (Sharknado 2: The Second One, Sharknado 3: Oh Hell No!, Sharknado: The 4th Awakens, Sharknado 5:
Global Swarming, and The Last Sharknado: It's About Time), as well as three spin-off films (Lavalantula, Sharknado: Heart of Sharkness, and 2 Lava 2 Lantula).
Though the original film was not explicitly a comedy, maintaining at least a façade of
seriousness despite the implausible plot, the sequels were more openly comedic in nature.
The film explores themes of california, helicopter, beach, tornado, hurricane.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and thought_provoking.